

# Céline Cosneau-Ampis

# **UX** Designer

## CONTACTS

c.cosneauampis@gmail.com 06.29.12.01.64

My LinkedIn - My Portfolio
Plaisir (78) - willing to relocate

#### SKILLS

User Research Personas

User Journey Map & User flows Information Architecture Wireframing & Prototyping User Testing HTML5 & CSS3

#### TOOLS

Adobe XD Figma Balsamiq Marvel InVision UsaHub Zeplin Atom GitHub

#### LANGUES

French: native

English: bilingual proficiency

Spanish: limited working proficiency

## **EDUCATION**

## UX Design Certification with a Front-End Specialization

Nov 2021 | CareerFoundry.com

1000+ hours project-based course focused on UX Design process & Front-end Development.

## Master 2 in Business Administration

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017 | KEDGE BS Bordeaux (FR) & Suzhou (CHINA)

#### ABOUT ME

UX Designer with a professional background in Non-Profit, Education and Care. Experienced in understanding people's true feelings, motivations and expectations as well as being proactive in solving problems. Skilled in creating intuitive user-centered experiences and prototyping with HTML and CSS.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Freelance UX Designer

London, Bournemouth (UK) & Plaisir (FR) | Oct 2020 - Present

Created mobile and web responsive applications design projects, from idea to prototype (more to come):

#### My Portfolio-Website

## My portfolio-website study case

I developed my own portfolio-website using Atom & GitHub, all while learning the basics of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.

#### **ExpertsNow - Responsive web application**

## ExpertsNow study case

Following a user-centered design process, I created a responsive web application. I conducted research, created prototypes, ran user tests and worked on the visual design.

#### MultiLearn - Mobile application

#### ← MultiLearn study case

Following a mobile-first design approach, I created a native application. I conducted research, created rapid prototypes and ran usability tests.

#### **Home Healthcare Provider**

CHCP | Morden (UK) | Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

Provided personal care to clients, made sure they were comfortable and quaranteed the maintenance of their environment.

## **Private English Tutor**

Acadomia & Complétude | Yvelines (FR) | Aug 2018 - Mar 2019 Individually tutored 8 and 5 students (5ème to Terminale).

## Coach (Youth worker)

Life Project 4 Youth | Cebu (PH) | Fev 2017 - Fev 2018

- Managed a programme gathering 15 youth coming from a disadvantaged economical environment.
- Acted as a consultant in a micro-activity developed by the Youth from the programme.
- Taught English, Computer & Communication skills to the Youth.
- Guided the Youth individually and per group towards their social and professional integration.